反恐24小时
第九季 第2集
以下事件发生在
中午12:00 至下午13:00 之间
基弗·萨瑟兰
伊冯娜·斯特拉霍夫
泰特
多诺万
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
威廉
德韦恩
格本加
阿金纳格贝
摩根特工
Agent Morgan.
贾尔斯·马特蒂
克羅伊·奧布賴恩就只帶了這些？
This is everything you got off Chloe O'Brian?
嗯，東西不多
Yeah, there wasn't much.
預付卡電話是偷來的
Prepaid from a stolen shipment.
有沒有查一下同一批的其他電話
Did you check the SIM card numbers from the rest of the shipment?
奧布賴恩的人也許會在用同一批電話
O'Brian's group might be using other phones from the same batch.
迈克尔·温科特
我們可以追蹤一下
We can run a trace.
嗯
Yeah.
這種事我們一般會找本地警方幫忙
Usually we get the local police to track them down.
本杰明·布拉特
但他們的流程會比較慢
Their procedures can be a little slow.
好吧，算了
Right. Well, never mind.
基姆·瑞弗
我有自己的流程
I've got my own procedures.
開車的老婆婆說
The old woman driving the car said
摩托車不知道從哪裏冒出來的
the motorcycle came out of the blue.
請稍等
Oh, hang on
客 串
米歇尔·费尔利
喂？
Hello?
是我，剛給你發了一個號碼
It's me. Listen, I sent you
是一個失竊的預付卡
the SIM number for a mobile phone
你幫我查一下同一批失竊的
from a stolen shipment. I need the numbers
其他電話的號碼
from every other phone in the same lot.
不行，都跟你說過我不會再幹這種事了
No, I've told you before. I won't do this anymore.
科林·萨尔蒙
罗斯·麦克科尔
越來越危險
It's getting too risky.
這事很重要，肯
This is important, Ken.
埃米莉·伯林顿
约翰·波耶加
乔瑟夫·米尔森
你的事都重要
It's always important.
要是我告訴你們局長（中央情報局）
What do you think your DCI is gonna think
你已經拿了我們三年的錢
when I tell him you've been on our payroll
斯蒂芬·弗雷
你覺得他會作何感想？
for the last three years?
那你自己也會惹一身麻煩
You'd be in just as much trouble as I would.
是嗎，我表示懷疑
You know, I seriously doubt that.
剪 辑
乔丹·戈德曼
好吧
All right, fine.
聽你的
I'll do it.
艺术指导
乔纳森·李
但這真的是最後一次了
But this is the very last time.
給你二十分鐘
You've got 20 minutes.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
她在這裏幹嘛？
What is she doing here?
我讓她復職了
I reinstated her.
等把鮑爾抓回來再說
Just until we get Bauer back.
讓她跟著你一起幹這事
I'm putting her on this with you.
長官？
Sir?
這是她應得的
And she deserves it.
只有她發現了鮑爾另有所圖
She's the only one who knew that Bauer was up to something.
那她怎麼就沒發現自己老公的行動？
Well, she wasn't that perceptive when it came to her husband.
聽著，她也許是想證明自己，這我沒意見
Look, she might be trying to prove something. That's fine.
制作人
伊恩·史密斯
但你怎麼能指望我
But you don't really expect me
跟她共事？
to be working with her
我指望你
I expect you
做自己的事，而不是質疑我的指令
to do your job without questioning my orders.
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
那個，好
That one. Good.
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
强·卡萨
监 制
大卫
弗瑞
监 制
罗伯特
科克伦
监 制
曼尼·科托
伊万·卡茨
监 制
霍华德·高登
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
编 剧
大卫·弗瑞
克羅伊！她回來了
My God, Chloe!
克羅伊？
Chloe?
我們還以為你走了
We thought you'd left us.
你這是怎麼了？
What happened to you?
呃
Um
克羅伊，你這樣子太慘了
Chloe, you look terrible.
沒事吧？
You okay?
三天？
Three days?
你到底去了哪裏？
Where in God's name have you been?
导 演
强·卡萨
被關在中情局秘密設施裏了
Locked in a CIA black site.
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
啥？
You what?
呃
Um
他們把我抓走的
They grabbed me.
翻译  lydia萌
我當時自己在運送補給
I was making a supply run on my own.
大意了，對不起
I was careless. I'm sorry.
你都供出去了什麼？
How badly are we compromised?
翻译  龙猫绕树跑
我什麼也沒說
I didn't say a word.
他們就這麼放了你？
So, they just let you go?
我，呃
I, uh
翻译  pizzamx
以前的一個同事把我救了出來
A guy I used to work with broke me out.
他讓我找個安全的地方呆著
Told me to go somewhere safe.
我知道聽起來有點不可思議
I know that sounds crazy.
校对  LordVader
是啊
Yeah, I mean
救你出來…這不可能啊
he broke you out... that's impossible.
對他來說不是問題
Not for him.
他以前是 CTU 的頭，叫傑克·鮑爾
He's a former head of CTU, Jack Bauer.
时间轴  筱宸葭
噢
Oh
统筹  饭离烨
我們得關門了
I have to shut it down.
大家馬上停止工作
We'll have to shut it down.
我們要換個地方了
We're moving to another spot.
別！
No!
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
特效 筱宸葭
他是想要保護我
He was trying to protect me.
都別動！
Nobody move!
傑克？
Jack?
把手放在我能看見的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
傑克，你幹嘛？
Jack, what are you doing?!
看來你是艾德裏安·克羅斯了
So, you're Adrian Cross.
嗯
Yes.
這幹嘛，什麼意思？
What is this? What's going on?
你就不用自我介紹了
No need to introduce yourself.
從我們拿到的文件裏
Certainly see enough of your name
已經看夠你的名字了
in the files we take.
你們哪個是德裏克·耶茨？
Which one of you is Derek Yates?
聽到沒有，你們哪個是德裏克·耶茨？
I said, "which one of you is Derek Yates?!"
耶茨已經不跟我們一起干了
Yates no longer works with us.
我們的工作風格不同
We had a clash of styles.
那你得幫我找到他
Then you're gonna help me find him.
這我可能難以從命了
I'm afraid I can't do that.
但我看你也沒別的選擇了
Yeah, I'm afraid you don't have any choice.
我們總是有選擇的，鮑爾先生
We always have a choice, Mr. Bauer.
所以客戶才會相信我們
That's what this organization represents.
要是幫了你，我豈不是就沒有信用可言了？
Were I to help you, what would happen to my credibility?
你的信用？
Your credibility?
我不會問你第三次
I am not gonna ask a third time.
住手，住手！我們幫你
Stop! Stop! We will help you.
我保證我會幫你
I promise. I will help you.
你為什麼要找耶茨？
Why are you looking for Yates?
我要知道他在做什麼
I need to know what he's doing.
否則沒法開始
Or else I can't begin to find him.
兩周前我截獲一份情報
Two weeks ago I intercepted intel
策劃刺殺海勒總統
framing an assassination attempt on president Heller.
計劃就是今天，在倫敦這裏實施
It's supposed to take place in London here today.
情報裏面唯一能找到的名字
The only hard name I could pick out
就是德裏克·耶茨
was Derek Yates.
我順藤摸瓜找到了他的組織
I tracked it to this organization.
也就是你這裏
Your organization.
你真要趟這趟渾水嗎，克羅伊？
You want that on your hands, Chloe?
耶茨太貪心了
Yates got greedy.
一起干沒多久就開始競價出售數據
Began selling data to the highest bidder
搞得跟拍賣行一樣
like it was some sort of auction house or something.
另外他還被我抓到
Also I caught him
入侵軍方的武器系統
hacking into military weapon systems.
為什麼？
Why?
這我就不知道了
I really don't know.
但我知道該讓他走人了
I knew it was time for him to go.
我不幹那種事情
I don't do that sort of thing.
那種直接下手的事情
Take direct action like that.
我們只是
We don't. We just
獲取並散佈信息
acquire information and disseminate it.
僅此而已
Nothing more.
說得好像是正經生意一樣
You make it sound like what you do is benign.
我們都心知肚明這是怎麼一種勾當
We both know it isn't.
是嗎？
Do we?
開始吧，克羅伊
Get started, Chloe.
我不想在這裏多呆一分鐘
I don't want to be here any longer than I have to.
彼特，檢查一下權限
Pete, make sure the others
確保大家都能進入到
have access to the closed- circuit surveillance system
倫敦的交通閉路監控系統
from the London transport.
哦好，哪一個？
Uh, okay, which ones?
所有的，我們需要做很多回溯檢索
All of them. We'll be doing lots of backtracing.
可能還需要捎帶服務器
We may need to piggyback servers.
切爾，把面部識別系統打開
Chell, pull up your facial recognition program.
要用它來過濾監控畫面
We'll use it for the cctv.
掃瞄任何與德裏克·耶茨相關的信息
We're gonna be scanning for any signs of Derek Yates.
你曾是我的朋友
You were my friend.
想要幫忙不妨直接開口
If you wanted my help, you should've just asked.
喂，巴什
Hey, bash.
那個混蛋耶茨還要在這裏呆多久？
How long's that junkie bastard Yates here for anyway?
放心，他是付了錢的
He's paying his way. Don't worry about it.
他那個馬子呢？有沒有幫她付她那一份？
How about her ladyship? Is he paying for her, too?
我說了「放心」
I said "don't worry about it."
好吧
Right.
我在幹活
I'm working.
你老是在幹活
You working too much.
要不要把你送到別的房間？
Do you want me to send you to the other room?
不要！
No!
那些男人好嚇人
Those men scare me.
為什麼不能去個好點的酒店？
Why can't we go to nice hotel?
那些可怕的人在保護我們，寶貝
Those scary men are protecting us, baby.
保護什麼？
Who from?
說曹操
Speak of the devil.
喂？你收到了嗎？
Yeah? Yeah, hi. Did you get it?
地狱导弹就绪
我正在看
I'm watching it now.
发 射
很不錯
Very impressive.
目标已摧毁
美國人應該不知道
And the Americans had no idea
是你在控制無人機吧？
that you were controlling the drone?
不，不會知道的
No, no, no, no, none.
我監聽他們的通訊好幾周
I monitored their comm traffic for weeks
才找到了一個合適的替罪羊，布好了證據
to find the perfect patsy, plant the evidence.
你還真是聰明呀
Aren't you clever.
那一切按進度進行？
So we're still on schedule?
寶貝
Baby
我沒聽清楚你說的話
I didn't hear what you said.
嗯，都按進度進行
Yeah, we're on schedule.
我提到那個修改要求也是？
Even with the modifications I requested?
寶貝，不要不理人家嘛
Baby, I don't care to be ignored.
什麼？
What?
能閉嘴嗎？
Would you shut up?!
噢是，差不多要搞定了
Yeah, uh, yeah, it's almost done.
你旁邊有人？
Is there someone there with you?
我問你話呢
I asked you a question.
沒，當然沒有，剛才只是…電視的聲音
No. No, of course not. It's just, it's the TV.
你沒跟別人說過這事吧？
You haven't told anyone else about this?
你的那些設備
About your device?
沒有
No.
好
All right.
我會帶錢在約定的地方見你
I'll be at the arranged place with your money.
但別讓我等你
But don't keep me waiting.
謝天謝地，格雷格，這事太扯了
Thank God. Greg, this is crazy.
他們都不讓我跟老婆說話
They won't let me talk to my wife.
我們按規矩辦事，中尉
Let's stick to ranks right now, lieutenant.
請坐
Sit down, please.
你知道這不是我幹的
You gotta know I didn't do this.
再說一遍發生了什麼事
Just tell me again what happened.
我當時正在操作 MQ-1 捕食者
I was piloting the mq-1 predator
為坎大哈郊外的一個車隊做巡邏和監控
doing recon and surveillance for a convoy outside kandahar.
谢泼德少校的車隊
Major Shepherd's convoy.
突然間無人機轉向西南
Out of nowhere, the drone suddenly banked to the southwest.
我認為是電腦的問題，就嘗試中止
I assumed computer failure, tried to abort.
但系統沒有反應
Systems wouldn't respond.
但就在那時導彈自己裝載上了
That's when the missiles armed themselves.
導彈可不會自己裝載自己
Missiles don't arm themselves.
但看上去就是那樣的
That's how it seemed.
好像是有另一個人在控制
It was like someone else had control.
所以那「另一個人」決定將谢泼德的車作為目標
So "someone else" decided to target Shepherd's vehicle
而這正好發生在他取消了你的週末休假之後
Right after he revoked your weekend pass.
這是你自己寫的
The man about whom you wrote
「我要把谢泼德這個賤人做掉
"I'm gonna put Shepherd down like the bitch he is.
是個人都受不了他這樣的」
There's only so much a man can take."
我沒寫過這些
I didn't write that.
這是我們從你經常訪問的一個軍事站點找到的
We got it off a military posting site you frequent.
日期是三周以前
Dated three weeks ago.
你覺得我有傻到
You think I'd be stupid enough
去寫這種東西？
to write something like that down?
人們憤怒的時候會說很多也會做很多事
People say and do a lot of things when they're angry.
少來了，你知道那不是我寫的！
Come on! You know that's not me!
你真覺得我是殺人犯？
You really think I'm a murderer?
我只知道死了四個人
I know four people are dead.
我的操作密鑰呢？
Where's my flight key?
憲兵拿走了
Mps took it.
看看裏面的數據
Check the data on it.
我所有的操作記錄都在裏面
It'll have all my keystrokes logged
它肯定能印證我的說法
back up what I'm saying.
已經檢查過了
It's been checked.
還跟機載記錄儀對比過
And cross-checked with the on board flight recorder.
所有指令都直接來自於你的控制台
Every command came directly from your console.
這事你一定要搞清楚，克裏斯
You gotta get to grips with this, Chris.
但你首先得交代清楚，否則我幫不了你
But I can't help you unless you own up to what you did.
準備好再跟我談的時候，跟憲兵說一下
You can let the MPS know when you're ready to talk to me.
格雷格，問題一定出自我的操作密鑰
Greg, the answer has to be on my flight key, okay?
我是被陷害的，我對上帝發誓！
I've been set up. I swear to God!
再查一次！
Check it again!
拜託了
Just, please.
一定漏掉了什麼，我確定
They're missing something, I know it.
漏掉了能還我清白的東西！
Something that'll clear me!
格雷格！
Greg!
這件事上你給我們的支持
I cannot tell you how much
真的讓我無法用言語感謝，阿拉斯泰爾
I appreciate your support on this, Alastair.
我知道你很難做
I know it hasn't been easy.
跟反對黨領袖在一起的時候就沒有輕鬆過
Well, sitting down with opposition leaders rarely is.
所以我一般不去找他們
That's why I do it as little as possible.
但我相信在今天這個場合，你的出席
But your presence here I believe will go a long way
一定能為我國續租貴國的基地
towards securing the votes needed
爭取到更多的選票
for an extension on the lease of your base.
奧德莉！首相先生
Audrey! Mr. prime minister.
請允許我介紹我女兒，奧德莉
I'd like you to meet my daughter, Audrey.
嗯，我們當然認識
Yes, we know each other of course.
今天這個招待會能請到這些人
Thank you so much for everything
還是多虧了你啊
you've done for the guest list for this reception.
謝謝，但這都是我手下的功勞
Thank you. I do have to give my staff all the credit.
很抱歉打斷一下
I'm sorry to interrupt you
但如果有空，馬克想跟您說句話
but mark needs to have a word with you when you have a moment.
您先去吧，首相先生跟我
I'm sure the prime minister and I can find plenty of things
一定有很多可聊的事情
to talk about until you return.
謝謝，阿拉斯泰爾
Thank you, Alastair.
閣下，我們剛剛收到消息
Sir, we just received word
一架美軍無人機在阿富汗向著我們自己的
an American drone fired a missile at one of our own
戰鬥車輛發射了導彈
armored vehicles in Afghanistan.
死了四個人
Four people were killed.
看起來是我們的飛行員的責任
It appears one of our own pilots is responsible.
死者裏面有兩名是英國軍官
Two of the dead were British officers.
上帝啊，我們自己人？
Oh, my God. By our hand?
是的，總統閣下
Yes, Mr. president.
這事會讓我們爭取保留迪戈加西亞
This incident is gonna wipe out the support we needed
無人機基地的努力全部化為泡影
to maintain our drone base in Diego Garcia.
我們得討論一下這事的影響
We have to discuss the implications
稍後吧，現在重要的是
Later. I think it's important
首相得從我嘴裏知道這事
that the prime minister hear this news from me.
等等
Hold on.
納瓦羅特工打來的
Agent Navarro.
什麼事，納瓦羅？
What is it, Navarro?
我一直想聯繫上您，長官
I've been trying to reach you, sir.
出了點情況，鮑爾逃走了
There's been a situation. Bauer escaped.
你什麼意思？不是剛剛才抓到的！
What are you talking about? You just apprehended him!
是的長官，但這也許正是
Yes, sir. Which may have been exactly
他的如意算盤
what he wanted.
什麼？
What?
他救出了另外一個嫌犯，他之前的一個同事
He broke out another prisoner, an ex-colleague of his.
現在看樣子鮑爾出現在倫敦
It appears that Bauer's purpose for being in London
就是為了去救她
was to effect that rescue.
你意思他沒有謀害海勒總統的計劃？
So you're saying he has no designs on president Heller?
從現在掌握的情況來看，應該不大可能
From what we know, it appears unlikely.
但你也不能確定 我的意思是
But you can't be sure. I mean
也許他救出這個同事
for all you know, he may need this colleague
也是為了下一步謀害總統
to carry out his attack on the president.
應該有這種可能
I suppose it's possible.
我該提醒下英國人麼？
Should I alert the brits?
不用，我們能應付
No. We have enough to contend with.
緝拿鮑爾的事由你負責，你最好是抓緊時間
It is on you to reacquire Bauer. And I'd do it quickly
否則你就捲鋪蓋走人
or you can kiss your career.
是，長官
Yes, sir.
不，我打電話不是問這個
No, that's not why I'm calling.
你最後一次看見耶茨是什麼時候？
When was the last time you saw Yates?
你朋友的紋身
Your friend's tattoo.
塞爾維亞黑手黨的符號，殺一個人就劃一道
It's serbian mob. One slash for each murder he's committed.
這四年你都在幹什麼？
What the hell have you been doing the past four years?
耶茨有消息麼？
What have you got on Yates?
地下沒有
Nothing on the underground.
我們要開始逐條街區的搜了
We're gonna start searching block by block.
抓緊
Work fast.
你為什麼要這麼做，傑克？
Why are you doing this, Jack?
幻想著阻止了這次襲擊
Some fantasy that if you stop the attack,
救了海勒，大家都會原諒你？
save Heller, all will be forgiven?
你就能回到女兒和家人身邊？
You can return back to your daughter and her family?
我回不去了，這跟那無關
There's no going back for me. It's not about that.
我告訴過你，這事遠不止海勒
I told you this is bigger than Heller.
不，你是說是為了艾德裏安好
No, you said that for Adrian's benefit.
但我瞭解你，傑克
But I know you, Jack.
非常瞭解
For better or worse.
你也瞭解海勒
You know Heller.
你知道他是個好人
You know he's a good man.
不，我不知道
No, I don't know that.
你還沒回答我的問題
And you didn't answer my question.
為什麼這麼做？
Why you?
我欠他的
I owe him.
也欠他家人的
I owe his family.
你是說奧德莉
You mean Audrey.
奧德莉和她爸爸是一路的
Audrey and her dad are part of the
他們差點把咱倆都毀了
same system that screwed us both.
至少我在試圖做點什麼與之抗衡
At least I'm doing something
怎麼做？
to fight against it. How?
靠洩露情報和軍事機密麼？
By leaking classified information? Military secrets?
戰場上的人們正在犧牲，克罗伊
People are out there dying in the field, Chloe.
情報機構保守那些機密
Intelligence agencies keep secrets
是因為他們在做的事情違法
because what they're doing is criminal.
你沒那麼笨
You're smarter than that.
我看見你在講話
I can see you talking
聽見的卻是艾德裏安的聲音
but all I can hear is Adrian Cross.
你沒資格教訓我，傑克
You don't get to judge me, Jack.
你不知道我的遭遇
Not after what I've been through.
斯托什，看這個
Hey, stosh, look at this.
這是一個戰地記者拍攝的原始素材
It's raw footage from an embedded reporter.
怎麼了？
What's going on?
這是阿富汗戰場上的一起誤傷事件
It's a friendly fire incident in Afghanistan.
軍事頻道有很多相關報道
There's a lot of chatter on the military channels.
一架美國無人機襲擊了一輛聯盟軍用車
An American drone attacked an allied military vehicle.
四人死亡
There's four people dead.
飛行員說他什麼都沒做
Pilot's saying he didn't do it.
並且懷疑是有人或什麼東西控制了這架飛機
Says someone or something took control of the drone.
他們信了？
They actually believe that?
這個飛行員從哪來的？
Where was this drone piloted from?
英國，下海福特空軍基地
Here in the U.K. Lower heyford air force base.
要用軍事戰略衛星系統跟蹤麼？
Tracked through milstar satellite system?
就是耶茨侵入的那個系統
That's the same system Yates was hacking into.
也許這就是他們企圖襲擊海勒的計劃
Maybe that's how they plan to attack Heller.
暗殺總統有很多比劫持無人機
There are easier ways to assassinate
更簡單的方法
a president than hijack a drone.
他們在傳達一個信息
Not if they're trying to make a point.
這次襲擊發生在阿富汗
This attack was in Afghanistan.
也許這是他們的一次演習
Maybe it was a dry run.
你該找個政府官員談談
I think you should talk to someone in the government.
找誰？沒人會信
O? No one would listen.
他們會把我當成恐怖分子，這是僅有的機會
They think I'm a terrorist. This is our only play.
我們得找到耶茨
We need to find Yates.
他在西伊令
He's in west ealing
藏在政府所屬一處房產裏
Hiding in a council estate.
你們叫他「政府工程」
"Projects" as you would call it.
你確定？
You sure?
恩
Mm-hmm.
消息倒是很可靠
Very good source on this one.
難的是這個
Here's the rub.
這片管這棟樓的是個叫做阿倫·巴什爾的毒販子
The bloke who runs the building is a heroin dealer named Aron Bashir.
他那群可愛的小朋友都叫他「破壞王」
"Basher" as he's known to his no doubt lovely friends.
不管怎樣，我們知道他是耶茨的供貨商
Anyway, we know he's Yates' supplier
而且是個混蛋，這是地址
and a bit of a nasty piece of work. The address.
謝謝
Thank you.
真想謝我就滾得遠遠的，再也別回來
You can thank me by leaving and never coming back.
你不能就這麼進去
You can't go in there blind.
我能黑進當地塔樓的監控系統
I can track the tower block's cctv system
但我得跟你去現場
but I need to be on site.
我不能讓你冒險
I can't ask you to do that.
我自願的
You're not.
你需要通訊支持
You're gonna need comm support.
拿上東西
Get what you need.
讓我去吧
Let me do this.
我會把他引開
I'll get him off our back.
找到耶茨，一切就結束了
Find Yates, and this will be over.
拉出一個衛星信號，覆蓋我們所在的區域
Pull up a satellite feed, cover us from there.
把廂車準備好
And get the van ready.
反对无人机
我要給首相打電話
I'm gonna call the prime minister.
正式提出要求
Make a formal request
讓我在議會上發言
to speak to parliament in session.
恕我直言，先生
With all due respect, sir
我，我不覺得這是個好主意
I-I-I don't think that's a good idea.
您可能會被圍攻
You'll be facing a hostile mob.
事實上，反對派已經在暗示
Already, the opposition is intimating
我們政府在粉飾此次的調查
that out government is whitewashing the investigation,
並且掩蓋了此次事件的一些事實
that certain facts of the incident have been covered up by us.
將軍
General.
無人機的駕駛員是誰？
Who was the drone pilot responsible?
克裏斯·坦納中尉
Lieutenant Chris Tanner.
把他帶過來要多久？
How long would it take to get him here?
閣下？
Sir?
我要你把他帶到這
I want you to bring him here
並且允許皇家憲兵隊在你的監督下審訊他
and allow the royal military police to interrogate him under your supervision.
閣下，將美國軍官移送外國司法裁判
Sir, handing over an American serviceman
有違我國的駐外部隊協議
to foreign jurisdiction is a violation of our status of forces agreement.
請盡快安排下去
Please, make the arrangements now.
你的意思我明白了
Your protest has been noted.
是
Sir.
您這次想讓事件透明化的姿態
This gesture of transparency
不會幫你贏得選票
is not gonna get you the votes you need.
但它能讓他們聽見我想說的話
But it may force them to hear what I have to say.
我不會準備演講
I'm not gonna prepare a speech.
我將誠心去表達歉意
I'm going to apologize from the heart.
讓他們意識到
Make them realize the threat
如果失去英國
to each and every one of us
將面臨怎樣的威脅
if we lose this island.
閣下，這同議會的行事風格不符
Sir, they do things differently in parliament.
他們不會對你的真誠無動於衷，馬克
They're gonna respond to honesty, mark.
就像大選期間那些選民
Just like the voters during the election.
我們在俄亥俄一度落後五個百分點
We were five points down in Ohio
可在市政廳舉行了集會後就一切都變了
when we did that town hall meeting.
您現在對付的
You're not addressing
不是一群猶豫不決的選民
a bunch of undecided farmers.
而是一圈老練
These are practiced
嗜血的立法者
legislators who want blood.
他們會轟你下台
Eye gonna shout you down,
會叫您騙子、殺人犯
they're gonna call you a liar
場面會很難看
they're gonna call you a murderer. It's brutal.
特別是對於一個
Especially for someone who
一個
who
什麼？
Who what?
一個什麼人？
Someone who what?
一個走下坡路的人
Who isn't at the top of their game.
你覺得我不行了？
Oh. You don't think that I'm up to this?
不，閣下，我覺得不行
No, sir, I-I don't.
你當初也覺得我在俄亥俄不行了
You didn't think I was up to Ohio, either.
謝謝你，馬克
Thanks, mark.
我剛剛碰到科伯恩將軍，他看起來臉色不太好
I just passed general Coburn. He looks really upset.
出了什麼事？
What is going on?
請讓我們單獨待會兒
Could we have the room, please?
你父親想去說服議會
Your father wants to talk to parliament.
我告訴他
I told him he'd be
那會讓他惹上大麻煩，可他不相信
walking into a massacre, but he-he won't believe me.
你得跟他談談
You've got to talk him out of it.
如果他堅信那是對的
Well, if he believes that it will work
我們為何不讓他試試
maybe we should let him try.
不，你不明白
No, you don't understand.
他們會發起全面進攻
They're gonna come at him from all sides.
他承受不了
He will not be able to handle that.
可你當初告訴我不用擔心
So when you told me not to worry
他之前出的岔子
about the slip that he made earlier
你只是要
were you just
我認真的
I meant it.
但你自己也說過
But you yourself said
壓力會讓他的病情加速惡化
the pressure can accelerate his decline.
你知道這對他多重要
You know how important this is to him. We
我們可以提前做好準備，我可以幫你
We can prepare him. I'll help you.
我們可以模擬一個辯論會
We'll do a debate prep session.
奧德莉
Audrey
馬克
Mark.
我們需要做的
All we have to do is get him
是幫他闖過這一關
through this trip.
美军无人机造成四人死亡
有英国军人遇害
友軍誤傷事件及傷亡者
Friendly fire, and the casualties
美军无人机造成四人死亡
有英国军人遇害
那是你幹的，對嗎？
This was you, yes?
是
Yep.
不會內疚麼？
You don't feel bad?
那些人早就死了
Those people were already dead.
只是他們不知道而已
They just didn't know it.
過了今天
After today,
末日時鐘的倒計只有一分鐘了
doomsday clock's set at one minute to.
整個世界將變成地獄
The whole world's going to hell.
世界末日？
End of the world?
美國總統將在國外遇刺身亡
The American president's gonna die on foreign soil.
諷刺地，有人會說詩意地
Ironically... some might say poetically
被美國無人機殺死
killed by American drones.
事情不會就此結束
That ain't gonna go unanswered.
多米諾第一張牌會倒下
Dominos are gonna fall
而我們則在格陵蘭，置身事外
and we're gonna sit it all out in Greenland.
格陵蘭？
Greenland?
對，一個美麗的地方
Yeah. Beautiful.
黃金、紅寶石礦藏
Gold, Ruby mines.
那裏的經濟發展也不是
An economy that doesn't
靠著搜刮小國家
depend on the subjugation of smaller countries.
很完美，再過
It's perfect. And in about
28分鐘
28 minutes
當我們完成交易
when we make the exchange
我就能負擔更比這裏更優越的環境了
I'm gonna be able to afford much more comfortable surroundings than this.
我瞭解這個跟我交易的賤人
But from what I know about this bitch I'm selling to
老天保佑，希望我能按時交貨
God help me if I don't deliver on time
所以你給我閉嘴，讓我把這個活幹完，好嗎？
so just shut up and let me get on with it, okay?
沒有跡象顯示鮑爾出現在
No sign of Bauer yet in our first pass
我們搜索的第一區域，他們找到了他逃跑坐的那輛車
at the search grid. They found the vehicle
但是沒有人在裏面
he escaped in empty and abandoned.
我在警察廳的線人打來電話
My source at the met came through.
被偷的貨箱裏有兩部電話，並且已被激活
There are two phones in the stolen shipment that are activated
位置很近
and close to one another.
你覺得是鮑爾和奥布赖恩?
And you think it might be Bauer and O'Brian.
很有可能
It's possible.
那兩部電話現在在哪裏？
Where are these phones now?
在西伊令的廉租房裏
A housing project in west ealing.
我不敢保證
Look, I can't promise you that
鮑爾就在那
Bauer's there, but right now
但這是我們現在掌握的最靠譜的線索了
it's as good a lead as we've got.
好吧，帶隊去查一查
All right, take a team, check it out.
巴什爾的那棟樓就在中間
Basher's building is in the middle.
好的
Okay.
傑克
Jack
耶茨沒有威脅
Yates isn't gonna be dangerous
但是，巴什爾那夥人則不同
but basher and his men are.
明白，謝謝
Got it, thanks.
你要多久能入侵
How long is it gonna take you
他們的閉路電視？
to access their closed-circuit television?
幾分鐘
A couple minutes.
我一進去馬上告訴你
I'll let you know as soon as I'm in.
好，試一下通訊系統
Okay, I want to test our comm units.
測試，一、二、三
Testing, one, two, three.
收到
Got it.
好的
Okay.
美国空军基地
皇家空军基地
下海福特
我向你們保證
I assure you
美國政府
the United States government
將全力對此次事件
will conduct a vigorous
展開公開透明的調查
and transparent investigation of this incident.
英國皇家憲兵
The royal military police
將可全面介入
will be granted full
對此次事件中的嫌疑人
access to lieutenant Tanner
克裏斯·坦納中尉展開調查
the individual we believe responsible.
總統先生
Mr. president.
這次事件會讓您的
Doesn't this incident call into question
篩查程序和，事實上
your screening procedures, and, in fact
您的整個無人機計劃遭到質疑麼？
the entire drone program itself?
每個美國戰鬥機飛行員
Well, every U.S. combat pilot
都經過了全面的心理評估
undergoes a thorough psychological evaluation.
並且我對篩選程序很有信心
And I am confident in that screening method.
那些被謀殺的士兵的家人
Are the families of the murdered soldiers
也應對此有信心麼？
supposed to take comfort in that?
當然不是
Of course not.
你要對那些孩子怎麼解釋
What do you say to the children
比如一個五歲的孩子
one as young as five
他的父親再也回不來了
whose fathers will never come home again?
他們有權知道答案，先生
They deserve an answer to that question, sir.
無意義的行動
There's never a good answer
從沒有合適的答案
for a senseless act.
你是說
So you're saying
但我會幫他們明白
But I would help them understand
他們愛的人是英雄
that their loved ones were heroes
真正的英雄
in the truest sense of the word.
為保護國家安全
Heroes who died fighting to make
而犧牲的英雄
this country safe.
他們的名字
Heroes whose names
會永遠銘刻在我心中
will remain in my heart forever.
對這個團隊的成員，我想說
And to the members of this body, I would say
如果你們退出戰鬥
if you withdraw from this fight
那這三人的死
the deaths of these three men
就會淪為投降的召喚
will serve as nothing more
毫無意義
than a call to surrender.
他們不該如此下場
They deserve better.
三個人，先生？
Three men, sir?
你該知道有四個人
You realize there were four men
死於襲擊
who died in the attack.
四個
Four.
你想把誰從傷亡名單中劃掉？
Who would you like to strike from the casualty list?
我猜不會是美國人
None of the Americans, I suppose.
我說了什麼，三個？
What'd I say, three?
那奧爾森隊長呢？
How about captain Olson?
他只有一個孩子，還是個女兒
He only had one child and it was just a daughter.
馬克
Mark
我很想知道，你能說出
I'm curious, can you, can you name
另一位死於襲擊的
the other British soldier
英國士兵嗎？
killed in this attack?
你還得看筆記嗎？
You have to consult your notes?
他不重要，不值得被記住嗎？
He's not important enough to remember his name?
這個你將會
This man who you will
「永遠銘刻在心中」的人
"hold in your heart forever"?
你連他名字都不記得？
And you can't remember his name?
他叫什麼名字？！
What's his name?!
你幹什麼，馬克
Damn it, mark.
看來我還有功課要做
I think I have a little work to do.
總統先生
Mr. president.
威爾金斯中尉
Lieutenant Wilkins.
已婚，有三個孩子
Married father of three.
上帝
God
他需要知道他將面對什麼
He needs to know what he'll be up against.
奧德麗
Audrey
看來巴什爾在前面安排了兩個人
Looks like basher's got two in the front
後面有一個，你看看什麼線索
one in the back. You see anything that
能幫我們找到耶茨躲在哪間屋裏？
could tell us which apartment Yates would be holed up in?
10層樓，200間屋子
There are ten floors and 200 flats.
哪間都有可能
He could be in any one of them.
巴什爾應該會把耶茨留在身邊
Basher would want to keep Yates close to him.
你能切斷後方的攝像頭信號嗎？
You think you could cut off the feed to the camera in the rear?
能
Yeah.
但會引人注意
Someone might notice.
我就是要引人注意
I'm counting on it.
米克
Mick.
Mick
幹嘛？
'Lo.
攝像頭失靈了
Camera's playing up.
媽的！巴什！
Bloody hell! Bash!
你們還站那幹嘛？
What are you all standing there for?
快下樓幫忙！
Go downstairs and help!
快去！有事通知我
Move! Let me know what's going on.
喊什麼呢？
What's all the shouting?
回屋裏去
Just get back in there
把自己鎖好
and lock yourself in.
去吧
Move.
快
Now.
有情況
I got something.
傑克，四樓
Jack, fourth floor.
兩個人正朝你去
Two of them, coming your way.
收到
Copy that.
傑克，右邊第二道門
Jack, it's the second door on the right.
都別緊張
Everybody stay calm.
我只想談談
I just want to talk.
放他走
Let him go.
你就是巴什吧
I take it you're Basher.
你跑來要談，你想怎樣
You're the one who came to talk. What do you want?
你在保護一個叫德裏克·耶茨的人
You're protecting a man named Derek Yates.
他現在能聽到我說話嗎？
Is there any chance he can hear me right now?
什麼事？
Why?
我想跟你談筆交易
'Cause I want to make you a deal.
什麼？用他換？
What? For him?
抱歉，對我來說不值得
Sorry, not really worth it on my end.
無意冒犯，米克
No offense, Mick.
不是換他的命
Not for his life.
是你的命
For yours.
我知道你們認為自己
Look, I can tell you consider yourself
很厲害
a pretty intimidating group.
你可能覺得我處於不利位置
You probably think I'm at a disadvantage.
我保證我不是
I promise you I'm not.
把德裏克·耶茨交給我，我就給你機會
You give me Derek Yates, and I give you the opportunity
全身而退
to walk out of here without being harmed.
我勸你接受
I suggest you take it.
真的？
Really?
我們得離開！
We're getting out of here!
他們很近了
They're close.
艾德裏安？
Adrian?
克羅伊，很快會有人找到你
Chloe, you're about to have some company.
一支車隊正朝你去
There's a convoy heading your way.
你確定他們是衝我們來的？
Are you sure they're for us?
絕對是中情局友人
Definitely tourists from Langley.
正快速接近
Closing fast.
他們一直在追蹤我們
They've been tracking us.
克羅伊，你必須離開
Chloe, you've got to get out.
那，就在那
There. Right there.
貨車裏的人，出來！
You in the van, come out!
最後一次機會！馬上從車裏出來
Last chance! Get out of the vehicle
高舉雙手
with your hands in the air now!
他們肯定沒走遠
They can't be far.
嘿！
Hey!
你在這棟樓裏見過這個人嗎？
Have you seen this man in the building?
見過，見過
Yeah, yeah.
他是個瘋子，就在樓上
He's crazy. He's upstairs.
他有槍
He's got a gun.
耶茨，不許動！
Yates, freeze!
鮑爾，放下武器，趴下
Bauer, put it down, and get on the ground!
馬上放下武器，鮑爾！
Drop the weapon now, Bauer!
別讓他們跑了！
Don't let them go!
武器放在地上！馬上放下！
Put it on the ground! Drop it now!
我放下武器！
I'm putting the weapon down!
快攔住那兩個人！
Just stop that couple!
摩根特工？
Agent Morgan?
拜託，你一定要相信我
Please, you got to trust me.
你得馬上讓你的人停止
Now, you need to tell your men to stop
他下去了！
He's heading down!
凱特！
Kate!
封鎖區域！
Locked down the area!
我們去抓鮑爾！
We've got Bauer!
馬上放下武器
Put the weapon down now.
慢慢，慢慢地
Slowly, slowly.
放到地上
All the way to the ground.
面朝車站起來
Up against the car.
你們追錯人了
You are chasing the wrong guy.
你似乎比其他人聰明點
Now, you seem smarter than the rest of them
所以我就告訴你一次
so I'm gonna tell you this once.
我在試圖阻止一起針對海勒總統的襲擊
I'm trying to prevent an attack on president Heller.
而你妨礙我了
And you are getting in my way.
真不應該
Now, that was a mistake.
摩根
Morgan.
摩根！
Morgan!
傑克，進來！
Jack, get in!
過去！
Move over!
有人受傷了！
We got a man down!
你哪來的車？
Where'd you get the car?
偷的
I stole it.
電線打火
I hotwired it.
幹得漂亮
Good job.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
只是擦傷
It just grazed me.
我沒事，但耶茨跑了
I'm fine, but Yates got away.
給，我從他中央處理器裏拿到的
Here, I got this from his cpu.
是什麼？
What is it?
電路圖，像是某種
Design schematics, some kind
多通道
of multi-channel
遙控系統
override system.
有十個模塊
There's ten modules.
是無人機
It's drones.
你說對了，傑克
You were right, Jack.
這個系統可以遠程控制
This system can commandeer
多達十架美國無人機
up to ten U.S. drones.
狗娘養的
Son of a bitch.
他們準備全面襲擊
They're planning a full-scale attack.
證據都在這
All the evidence is here
向相關機構報警
to alert the authorities.
他們能破譯數據
They can decrypt the data.
好，很好
Okay, good.
不要，不不不不！
No! No, no, no, no, no!
怎麼了？
What's happening?
耶茨嵌入了一個自毀系統
Yates embedded a self-destruct program.
數據在自行刪除
It's erasing itself.
能保存嗎？
Can you save it?
克羅伊，保存！
Chloe, save it!
沒法保存，程序刪除了我的硬盤
Couldn't do it. It was erasing my hard drive.
只剩下一部分電路圖
All I have is the piece of the schematic.
狗娘養的
Son of a bitch.
好吧，耶茨帶著一個硬殼箱
Okay, Yates was carrying a hard-shell case.
裝置肯定在那裏面
The device must be in there.
我們得馬上追上他們！
We need to pick up his trail now!
可不知道他在哪
Yeah, he could be anywhere.
從塔樓的閉路電視找起
Start with the closed-circuit tvs from the towers.
他朝南去了
He was heading South.
該死！
Damn it!
沒事了吧？
Are we okay?
好像是的
Yeah, yeah. Looks like it, yeah.
多待一會兒
Just want to hang here a little while longer.
安全起見
Just to be safe.
你的活兒呢？
What about your work?
都完成了
It's all done.
找到新買家就行了
Just got to find a new buyer.
找新買家？
A new buyer?
為什麼？
Why?
追我們的那個人
Guy who chased us
你覺得是誰派來的？
who do you think sent him?
瑪戈
Margot.
你怎麼知道？
How do you know?
殺了我
Well, why pay when you can kill me
拿到裝置就不必花錢了
and get the device for free?
卑鄙的賤人
Devious bitch.
寶貝
Oh, baby.
不過沒事
Yeah, but it's all right. Mmm.
我們還是能撈一大筆
We're still gonna clean up.
有的是人想要
Plenty of people want
買這個小東西
to pay for this little baby.
馬上回來
Back in a minute.
再來兩杯
Two more.
好的
Yeah, all right.
你真厲害
You-you are unbelievable.
可是我想要你
Oh, but I want you.
現在就要
Now.
可是
Well
你喜歡公共場合，是嗎？
Geez, you love doing it in public places, don't you?
可你總要等我
Mm-hmm. You are gonna
方便完的啊，寶貝
have to actually wait till I finish, baby.
嗨，是我
Hi, it's me.
我拿到裝置了，但是有個問題
I've got the device, but there was a problem.
什麼問題？
What?
有人在追我們
Someone came after us.
一個美國人
An American.
我不知道他是誰
I don't know who he was.
我以前從沒見過他
I've never seen him before.
我們勉強才脫身
We barely got away.
你確定沒人跟著你？
Are you sure you're not being followed?
確定
Yes.
德裏克以為你出賣了他
But Derek thought you double-crossed him.
說要找新買家
Started talking about finding another buyer.
所以
So
你把他處理了
You took care of it.
是的
Yes.
乖女兒
That's my girl.
盡快回家
Come home as soon as you can.
媽咪在等你呢
Mommy's waiting.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs